expressbitcoinpostage.com 2018-08-21

# Privacy & Return Policy – Express Bitcoin Postage

You may return any unused labels within a time period of 14 days. You must provide proof of purchase. Once you initiate the refund request, it may take several days for the carrier to verify the return and issue credit. Once credit has been issued, the label is null and void and cannot be mailed. Once we receive notification that a credit has been issued, we will notify you and issue that credit to your account. We do not charge any fees to process any refunds unless the carrier imposes them.

This privacy policy sets out how “ExpressBitcoinPostage.com” uses and protects any information that you give “ExpressBitcoinPostage.com” when you use this website. Our site is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

#### What we collect 

**We may collect the following information:**

Name and contact information including email address

#### What we do with the information we gather

**We require this information to process your orders**  
We use your name and contact information for both the sender and receiver in order to requisition the appropriate services that you order such as shipping labels. We send this information to the shipping carriers you choose so that they can fulfill your order and generate the appropriate shipping labels for you.

**Internal record keeping.**  
We may use the information to provide customer service (such as checking on order status or helping with refunds) and to improve our products and services. We will never sell your information.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law.**
